Guide to the Center for American Music Photos CAM.PHOTOS.2017
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Letter from Stephen Foster to William Hamilton, page 2 and 3, January 16, 1857 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17073)
- Manuscript "Open Thy Lattice, Love," p. 1 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17074)
- Exterior of the Stephen Foster Memorial Home at 3600 Penn Avenue (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17075)
- Side by side images of William Foster, Jr., and Jessie Lightner (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17234.01)
- Extracted image of Jessie Lightner (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17234.02)
- Side by side images of Edward Y. Buchanan and Ann Eliza Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17235)
- Letter from Stephen Foster to E.P. Christy, June 20, 1851 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17236)
- Letter from Stephen Foster to E.P. Christy, June 12, 1851 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17237)
- Manuscript of "Oh Boys, Carry Me 'Long," pages 1 & 2 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17238)
- Manuscript of "Oh Boys Carry Me 'Long," page 3 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17247)
- Manuscript of "Oh Boys Carry Me 'Long" verses two and three set to music (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17248)
- Letter from Frederick Steele to Oliver Barrett, Nov. 18, 1922 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17570)
- Drawing of Foster leaning on his arm (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17571.01)
- Negative image of 17571.01, drawing of Foster leaning on his arm (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17571.02)
- Manuscript "For Thee, Love, For Thee," page 1 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17572)
- Manuscript "For Thee, Love, For Thee," page 2 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17573)
- Manuscript "I Would Not Die in Spring Time," page 1 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17580)
- Manuscript with "Music by Byerly" written at the top (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17581)
- Display window at L.S. Ayres & Company Washington Street on Foster and John Tasker Howard's book, with numerous relics from the collection, January 13, 1934 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 18166)
- Exterior of Foster Memorial Home (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19377)
- Autographed photo of Lorraine Foster inscribed to Mr. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19378)
- Page 5 of the Foster Hall Bulletin, February, 1935 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19448)
- Lithograph of Robert Peebles Nevin (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19449)
- Josiah K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19460)
- Reverend Joseph Stockton (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19478)
- Mr. John Kelly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19479)
- Letter from Eliza Foster to William B. Foster, Jr., p. 1, May 14, 1832 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Folder 19480)
- Letter from Eliza Foster to William B. Foster, Jr., p. 2, May 14, 1832 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19481)
- Letter from Eliza Foster to William Foster, Jr., p. 3, May 14, 1832 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19482)
- Letter from Eliza Foster to William B. Foster, Jr., p. 4, May 14, 1832 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19483)
- Letter from William B. Foster to William B. Foster Jr., page 1, Sept. 3, 1841 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19484)
- Letter from William B. Foster to William B. Foster Jr., page 2, Sept. 3, 1841 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19485)
- back of letter showing address, from William B. Foster to William B. Foster, Jr., Sept. 3, 1841 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19486)
- Marion Foster and two friends (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Folder 19487)
  - Image of three young women (one is possibly Marion Foster but this likely a misidentification) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19487.01)
  - Close up of one of the young women from 19487.01 believed to be Marion Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 19487.02)
- Forged Foster portrait allegedly by Thomas Hicks (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Folder 22719)
  - Portrait of Stephen Foster by Thomas Hicks (portrait is a forgery) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 22179.02)
  - Close up of Thomas Hicks portrait of Stephen Foster (portrait is a forgery) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 22179.01)
- Black and white portrait of the Foster Memorial from the museum wing (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 22180)
- Portrait of the Reverend William Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 22181)
- Foster's flute with reproductions of "Jeanie" and "Come with Thy Sweet Voice Again" in the background (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 22182)
- Rachel E. Woods, wife of Henry Woods (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 22334)
- Henry Woods (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 22335)
- Forged letter from Stephen Foster to William A. Pond, July 6, 1863 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 22561)
- Charles Copeland sketch of a young girl sitting beside a well (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 22958)
- Side by side images of the front and back of a medal for Josiah K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 23869)
- Front side of medal presented to Josiah K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 23869a)
- Pencil sketch of C. J. Haden (established Foster Memorial in Fargo, Georgia) by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 23950)
- Letter from S. Reed Johnston to Morrison Foster, February 12, 1886 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 24799)
- Letter from Morrison Foster to S. Reed Johnston, pages 1 and 4, February 14, 1886 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 24800)
- Letter from Morrison Foster to S. Reed Johnston, pages 2 and 3, February 14, 1886 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 24801)
- Steamship "The Telegraph" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 24889)
  - Close up of steamship "The Telegraph" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 24889.01)
  - Steamship "The Telegraph" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 24889.02)
- Four small photos including M. F. Welch, D. C. and J. W. Rose, and J. G. and S. C. Boggs, on the steps of the Foster Memorial Home (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25427)
- The Tuesday Musical Club performing on the stage of the Stephen Foster Memorial, 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25586)
- Stage in auditorium of Stephen Foster Memorial showing J. K. Lilly addressing audience at dedication of Memorial, 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25587)
- J. K. Lilly presenting Foster Hall Collection to Chancellor Bowman of the University in the auditorium of Stephen Foster Memorial, 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25588)
- Exterior of the Foster Memorial at night, shot from the museum wing (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25589.01)
- Exterior of the Foster Memorial at night, side view from Museum wing side (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25589.02)
- Drawing of Josiah K. Lilly by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25599)
- Pencil sketch of T. D. Rice by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25600)
- Pencil sketch of Mary Elizabeth Johnson by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25601)
- Pencil sketch of Mary Alice Wilson by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25602)
- Front doors of the Memorial at night (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25628)
- Front doors of the Memorial and museum wing during the day (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25629)
- The Stephen Foster Memorial and the Cathedral of Learning, shot from Forbes Avenue (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25630.01)
- The Cathedral of Learning and Stephen Foster Memorial shot from across Forbes Avenue (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25630.02)
- Aerial view of the Stephen Foster Memorial, shot from the museum wing side (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25631)
- The Cathedral of Learning, shot from Fifth Avenue (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25632)
- Exterior of Stephen Foster Memorial, view from museum wing lawn (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25633.02)
- Exterior of Foster Memorial shot from the loading dock side (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25634)
- Exterior of Foster Memorial, shot from museum wing (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25635)
- Reading room of the Foster Memorial (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25636)
- Foster Memorial exhibit area showing entrance (closed off now) into back office (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25637)
- Foster's melodeon against a backdrop of Foster Hall Reproductions in the Stephen Foster Memorial museum (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25638.02)
- Entrance to the Foster museum, showing arches (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25638)
- Stephen Foster museum, looking through arch into museum corridor (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25639)
- View of the museum passageway through a museum archway (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25639.01)
- View of the museum passageway through a museum archway (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25639.02)
- Close up of tablet dedicated to Josiah K. Lilly in the corridor wall of the Stephen Foster Memorial (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25640)
- Northeast corner of the Stephen Foster Memorial lobby (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25641.01)
- Northwest corner of the Stephen Foster Memorial lobby (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25641.02)
- Interior of the Stephen Foster Memorial auditorium, showing the seating (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25642)
- Museum corridor of the Stephen Foster Memorial (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25647)
- Social room in the lower level of the Stephen Foster Memorial (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25648)
- Tuesday Musical Club string quartet performing on the stage of the Stephen Foster Memorial auditorium (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25678)
- Seating in the Stephen Foster Memorial Auditorium (now the Charity Randall Theater), view from the stage (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25679)
- Negative, painting of Matthew Prior, January 24, 1941 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25761)
- Silhouette of Foster on background of "My Old Kentucky Home, Good Night" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25896)
- Framed silhouette of Stephen Foster with a written dedication to "My friend John Mahon" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25988)
- Silhouette of Stephen Foster with a written dedication to "my friend William Pond" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25989)
- Framed silhouette of Stephen Foster with a written dedication to George Cooper (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25990)
- Framed silhouette of Stephen Foster with a written dedication to John Mahon (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25991)
- Matthew Wiley Welch (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25992)
- Allegheny Cemetery: including M. F. Welch, M. W. Welch, J. W. Rose, and J. D. Rose, January 13, 1993 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25993)
- Allegheny Cemetery, D. C. Rose, J. W. Rose, and others, January 13, 1927 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25994)
- Young women singing at Foster's gravesite at Allegheny Cemetery, 1927 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25995.01)
- Young women singing at Foster's gravesite at Allegheny Cemetery, 1927 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25995.02)
- Dallas Rose, Great grandson of Stephen Foster, placing a wreath on Foster's grave, 1927 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25996)
- Crowd gathered at Foster's gravesite for memorial celebration, 1927 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25997)
- Allegheny Cemetery, J. O. Taylor laying wreath, W. Rhodes, H. M. Dermitt, and W. B. Foster, January 13, 1931 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 25998)
- Allegheny Cemetery, J. W. Rose, M. F. Welch, J. K. Lilly, M. W. Welch, D. J. Rose, F. Hodges, et cetera, January 13, 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26000)
- Allegheny Cemetery, J. W. Rose, H. M. Dermitt, F. Hodges, and others, January 13, 1939 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26001)
- Allegheny Cemetery, Jeff Davis King laying a rose on Foster's grave, January 13, 1941 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26003)
- Allegheny Cemetery, Dr. Nash placing a wreath on Foster's grave, January 13, 1942 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26004)
- Foster Hall Quartet: G. M. Robinson, H. Campbell, C. Somvels, W. Woolfolk and C. Hicks at Allegheny Cemetery, January 13, 1933 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26005)
- Dr. Evans at Allegheny Cemetery, 1938 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26007)
- Allegheny Cemetery. Left to Right: Alexander Dallas Rose, Dr. Evans, 3rd Presbyterian Church; Mrs. Rose (granddaughter); Burton Muslin, Representative of the Piano [ ]; one other unidentified name, January 13, 1937 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26008)
- Mrs. Alexander Dallas Rose at the Allegheny Cemetery, January 13, 1924 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26009)
- Chorus of school children at Foster's gravesite in Allegheny Cemetery, January 13, 1924 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26010)
- Foster family plot at Allegheny Cemetery (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26011.01)
- Foster family plot at Allegheny Cemetery (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26011.02)
- Foster service, 1929 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Folder 26012)
  - Unidentified crowd at Allegheny Cemetery for Foster service, 1929 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26012.04)
  - Unidentified crowd at Allegheny Cemetery for Foster service, 1929 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26012.03)
  - Unidentified crowd at Allegheny Cemetery for Foster service, 1929 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26012.02)
  - H. Marie Dermitt, Marshall Foster Reed, Dorothy Jane Rose, and Mrs. Alexander Rose at Allegheny Cemetery, 1929 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26102.01)
- Foster service, January 13, 1940 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Folder 26103)
  - Foster service: J.K. Lilly and Fletcher Hodges, Jr. at Allegheny Cemetery following the Memorial program, January 13, 1940 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26013.01)
  - Foster service: people at the grave of Stephen Foster, January 13, 1940 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26013.02)
  - Foster service: Stephen Foster grave service, January 13, 1940 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26013.03)
  - Foster service: people placing flowers on Foster's grave, January 13, 1940 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26013.04)
  - Foster service: people standing by Foster's grave, January 13, 1940 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26013.05)
  - Foster service: Foster's gravesite, January 13, 1940 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26013.06)
  - Foster service: People standing at Foster's gravesite, January 13, 1940 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26013.07)
- Photo of "Stephen C. Foster Commemoration at the grave in Allegheny Cemetery" 1935. Edward Montgomery Atty, representative of the Aullers composers + Publishers association and Hill Dermitt, Secretary civic club of Allegheny County (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26014)
- Photo of an unknown woman laying a wreath at the grave of Stephen C. Foster, January 13, 1924 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26015)
- Photo of a children's choir singing at the grave of Stephen Collins Foster, January 13, 1924 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26016)
- Photo of William B. Foster, grandnephew of Stephen C. Foster at the grave of SCF, January 13, 1930 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26017)
- The first public commemoration of the anniversary of the death of Stephen C. Foster. "Left to Right:-Rev. Harry B. Heald, Rector of St. Andrew's Protestant Episcopal Church; Mrs. H. Talbot Peterson, member of the Civic Club Community Music Committee; Mrs. Alexander Dallas Rose, granddaughter of the composer; Miss H. Marie Dermitt, Secretary of the Civic Club of Allegheny County; Dallas Rose, great-grandson of Foster; Mrs. E.B. Lee, member of the Municipal Music Committee of the Civic Club; Mrs. Charles T. Manning, relative of Foster; Miss Emelie McCreery, member of the Municipal Music Committee of the Civic Club; Mrs. Ralph L. Hill, Dr. Ralph L. Hill, friends of the Foster family; Mr. Rose and Carl Whitmer, members of the Municipal Music Committee of the Civic Club, 1923 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26018)
- Arthur Nevin, composer and brother of Ethelbert Nevin, laying the Civic Club wreath on the grave of Stephen C. Foster, January 13, 1942 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26019)
- "Kostalauch, April, 1941" laying "The Civic Club" wreath at the grave of Stephen C. Foster. "Left to Right: William J. O'Briem, Jr., Western Pennsylvania Manager for American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers. Miss Helene Beegle. Walter Horigan, Chairman of the Memorial Art Association, Mrs. Alexander Dallas Rose, Granddaughter of Stephen C. Foster. Back of Mrs. Rose is Fletcher Hodges, Curator of the Foster Memorial of the University of Pittsburgh. Burton H. Mustin, prominent musician and Chairman of the Stephen C. Foster Commemoration Committee of the Civic Club of Allegheny County. Mrs. Dorothy Rose Melady, Great Granddaughter of Stephen C. Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26020)
- "Kostalauch, April, 1941" laying "The Civic Club" wreath at the grave of Stephen C. Foster. "Left to Right: William J. O'Briem, Jr., Western Pennsylvania Manager for American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers. Miss Helene Beegle. Walter Horigan, Chairman of the Memorial Art Association, Mrs. Alexander Dallas Rose, Granddaughter of Stephen C. Foster. Back of Mrs. Rose is Fletcher Hodges, Curator of the Foster Memorial of the University of Pittsburgh. Burton H. Mustin, prominent musician and Chairman of the Stephen C. Foster Commemoration Committee of the Civic Club of Allegheny County. Mrs. Dorothy Rose Melady, Great Granddaughter of Stephen C. Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26021)
- "Kostalauch, April, 1941" laying "The Civic Club" wreath at the grave of Stephen C. Foster. "Left to Right: William J. O'Briem, Jr., Western Pennsylvania Manager for American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers. Miss Helene Beegle. Walter Horigan, Chairman of the Memorial Art Association, Mrs. Alexander Dallas Rose, Granddaughter of Stephen C. Foster. Back of Mrs. Rose is Fletcher Hodges, Curator of the Foster Memorial of the University of Pittsburgh. Burton H. Mustin, prominent musician and Chairman of the Stephen C. Foster Commemoration Committee of the Civic Club of Allegheny County. Mrs. Dorothy Rose Melady, Great Granddaughter of Stephen C. Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26022)
- "Kostalauch, April, 1941" laying "The Civic Club" wreath at the grave of Stephen C. Foster. "Left to Right: William J. O'Briem, Jr., Western Pennsylvania Manager for American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers. Miss Helene Beegle. Walter Horigan, Chairman of the Memorial Art Association, Mrs. Alexander Dallas Rose, Granddaughter of Stephen C. Foster. Back of Mrs. Rose is Fletcher Hodges, Curator of the Foster Memorial of the University of Pittsburgh. Burton H. Mustin, prominent musician and Chairman of the Stephen C. Foster Commemoration Committee of the Civic Club of Allegheny County. Mrs. Dorothy Rose Melady, Great Granddaughter of Stephen C. Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26023)
- Jessie W. Rose and Eugene L. Connelly, January 13 (later than 1941), at Allegheny Cemetery, Pittsburgh PA. Stamped "N.M. Jeannero/ Post-Gazette" in lower right corner (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26024)
- Mrs. Alexander Dallas Rose, Granddaughter of Stephen C. Foster at in the Stephen Foster Memorial museum, circa 1941 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26025)
- Jessie W. Rose, Paul R. Jones, and Jeanie Moore, in the Stephen Foster Memorial Museum, January 13, 1944 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26026)
- Dr. Ralph Hill, participant in January 13, 1988 memorial program for Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26027)
- Visitors to Foster's grave, August 14, 1941 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Folder 26028)
  - Foster's gravestone at Allegheny Cemetery, August 14, 1941 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26028.01)
  - Unidentified man at Foster's grave, August 14, 1941 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26028.02)
  - Unidentified boy at Foster's grave, August 14, 1941 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26028.03)
- Foster Service at Allegheny Cemetery, 1990 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Folder 26029)
  - Foster Service at Allegheny Cemetery: Crowd, including school children, at Foster's gravesite (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26029.01)
  - Foster Service at Allegheny Cemetery: Crowd, including school children, at Foster's gravesite (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26029.02)
  - Foster Service at Allegheny Cemetery: Deane Root speaking at Foster's gravesite (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26029.03)
  - Foster Service at Allegheny Cemetery: Deane Root speaking at Foster's gravesite (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26029.04)
  - Foster Service at Allegheny Cemetery: Representative of Allegheny Cemetery speaking at Foster's gravesite (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26029.05)
  - Foster Service at Allegheny Cemetery: children standing near Foster's gravesite (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26029.06)
  - Foster Service at Allegheny Cemetery: Unidentified woman speaking at Foster's gravesite (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26029.07)
- Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery and Trinity Cathedral, 1989 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26030)
  - Proof sheet of Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery and Trinity Cathedral (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26030.01)
  - Proof sheet of Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery and Trinity Cathedral (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26030.02)
  - Proof sheet of Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery and Trinity Cathedral (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26030.03)
- Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery, 1989 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Folder 26031)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: Foster's gravesite festooned with wreaths (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.01)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: Fletcher Hodges, Jr., at Allegheny Cemetery (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.02)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: people and school children gathered at Allegheny Cemetery (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.03)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: Teruko Shiono and an unidentified woman at Allegheny Cemetery (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.04)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: Foster's gravesite covered in wreaths (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.05)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: A band plays brass instruments near Foster's grave (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.06)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: School children gather at Foster's gravesite (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.07)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: Deane Root and an unidentified man near Foster's grave (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.08)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: Colorguard standing at attention while Tom Starsenic speaks near Foster's gravesite (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.09)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: Color guard standing at attention near Foster's grave (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.1)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: Tom Starsenic standing near an unidentified woman who is addressing the crowd (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.11)
  - Foster commemoration events at Allegheny Cemetery: Colorguard standing at attention near Foster's grave (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26031.12)
- Side by side images of postage sized-sized tintype of Foster in gold frame (one original size, one blown up) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26163)
- Drawing of Old Dog Tray from The Songs of Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26195)
- Adaptation of "Daguerreotype pose" on card, inscribed to B. Read (?) by M. Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 26537)